A Guide to the Robert T. Muse Papers, 1958-2014
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Research/Source Files., Extent: 34 boxes. (Box 9-43)
  - F:DY Elizabeth Bouch (Silver Spring MD). (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - F:DZ Joe Sissom (Irving TX). (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - F:EA Nancy Kuehl (Bryan TX). (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - F:EB Wilma Diesen (Midland MI). (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - F:EC Jeanette Eilbeck (Fairfield CA). (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - F:ED Ben Muse (Juneau AK). (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - F:EF Kaye Brown (West End NC). (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - F:EG James Huber (Section AL). (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - F:EH Robert Albert Jr. (Fillmore CA). (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - F:EI Heritage Place (Kinston NC). (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - F:EJ Karen Muse (Woodstock GA). (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - F:EK 1990 Muse Reunion. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - F:EL Wilma L. Muse (Arden NC). (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - F:EM Chris Anderson (Lancaster OH). (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - F:EN Bettie Belle Muse Watson (Kentwood LA). (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - F:EN Bettie Belle Muse Watson (Kentwood LA) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:EO Hazel Grimes (Ft. Worth TX). (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - F:EP Hattie Mae Muse (Carrollton GA). (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - F:EQ Thomas B. Moseley (Clifton TX). (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - F:ER Newberry Library (Chicago). (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - F:ES Winchester VA. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - F:ET Kay Muse Bolliger (Winchester VA). (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - F:EV Edward Earl Muse Jr. (Clearwater FL). (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - F:EW Linda S. Darley (Griffin GA). (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - F:EW Daniel Brown (Corvallis OR). (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - F:EX September 1991 Salt Lake City Trip. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - F:EY Jerry A. Muse (Stockport OH). (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - F:EZ Robert Warren Muse (Auburn NE). (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - F:FA North Carolina Research - Post-1991 Reunion. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - F:FB Jerry Muse (Ravenel SC). (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - F:FC Mammie Anderson (Johnson City TN). (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - F:FD Charles Kenneth Muse (Topeka KS). (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - F:FG Harold Firtik (Berwyn IL). (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
  - F:FG Harold Firtik (Berwyn IL) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:FG-2 Harold Firtik (Berwyn IL). (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - F:FH Penelope Culver (West Helena AR). (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - F:FI January 1992 North Carolina and Atlanta Trip. (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - F:FJ Harlan Muse. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - F:FK February 1992 Virginia Research - Blacksburg, Leesburg, Ashburn, Manassas. (Box 28, Folder 10-11)
  - F:FL Greg Howearth (Cedar City UT). (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - F:FM Darlene O'Steen (Apex NC). (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - F:FN Alan W. Muse (Fort Worth TX). (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - F:FN-2 Alan W. Muse (Fort Worth TX). (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - F:FO Gloria Palmer (Grass Valley CA). (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - F:FP Jerry Benedict (Austin TX). (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - F:FQ Harry L. Muse (Wantagh NY). (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - F:FR Billie G. Muse (Burleson TX). (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - F:FS Shelby Holder (Texarkana AR). (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - F:FT 1992 England Trip. (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
  - F:FV Duke University, Virginia State Library, Tappahannock VA Courthouse. (Box 29, Folder 12-14)
  - F:FV Duke University, Virginia State Library, Tappahannock VA Courthouse (Rolled Item). (Box 44, Folder n/a)
  - F:FW Louise Randall Camp (Albuquerque NM). (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - F:FW Louise M. Blue (Carthage NC). (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - F:FX Anita Reed (Memphis TN). (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - F:FY Vickie Weymouth (Midlothian VA). (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - F:FZ George Muse (Manhattan Beach CA). (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - F:GA Thomas Swatloski (New Iberia LA). (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - F:GB Marion Ritter (St. Augustine FL). (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - F:GC Zack Joseph Lee (Sarasota FL). (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - F:GD Tim Hatfield (Santa Barbara CA). (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - F:GE 1992 Muse Reunion. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - F:GF Mrs. Guy Weston Wall (Blacksburg VA). (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - F:GH Sue Riner (Jesup GA). (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - F:GI Terri Jean Adams (Jupiter FL). (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - F:GJ Lynn Tolleson Goen (Chesnee SC). (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - F:GK Charles Taylor (Hollywood FL). (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - F:GL Sarah Wall (Blacksburg VA). (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - F:GM Barbara Leimback (Burley WA). (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - F:GN February 1993 Richmond Archives Trip. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - F:GO Gabrielle Bryant (Incline Village NV). (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - F:GP Suzzette Greth Yandle (Georgetown TX). (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - F:GQ Virginia Regan (Terrytown LA). (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - F:GR Peggy R. McAndrew (Rocky Mount VA). (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - F:GS Gwendolyn Platt (Dunnellon FL). (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - F:GT Mary A. Matson (Charlottesville VA). (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - F:GU March 1993 Richmond and Raleigh Archives Trip. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - F:GV Dorothy McCowen (Fremont CA). (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - F:GW Wildra Welch (Salt Lake City UT). (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - F:GX 1993 Salt Lake City Trip. (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - F:GY Alice Whitehead (Shreveport LA). (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - F:GZ Tim Hudson (Waterloo Ontario). (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - F:HA Daniel McKillop (Springfield OR). (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - F:HB Ray Bryan Womack (Palmdale FL). (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - F:HC Geraldine Bailey (Kirkwood MO). (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - F:HC 1993 Atlanta Archives Trip. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - F:HD Peggy Muse (Lexington KY). (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - F:HE Carol Tillman Bullins (Asheboro NC). (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - F:HF Annie Reagan (Laurinburg NC). (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - F:HG Dan Muse (El Cajon CA). (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - F:HG James Harold Muse (El Cajon CA) - Family Tree Maker Site. (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
  - F:HI Louise Seawell (Carthage NC). (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - F:HI Jay Muse (Shawnee Mission KS). (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - F:HK Tom Aldred (Sunbury NC). (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - F:HL Gail Johnson (Union City TN). (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - F:HM Laura Ann Moseley (Camp Verde AZ). (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - F:HO Doug Hale (New Bern NC). (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - F:HP Melva Muse Stockton (Covina CA). (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
  - F:HP Melva Muse Stockton (Covina CA). (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - F:HQ John Squires (Brentwood CA). (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - F:HR Elizabeth Jenkins (Charlotte NC). (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - F:HS Olive Walmer (McKean PA). (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - F:HT Connee Kroeger (Deer Park TX). (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - F:HU Lela Board (Pahrump NV). (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - F:HV William Robert Muse (Roseburg OR). (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - F:HW June Southall (Eldorado AR). (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - F:HX Catherine Hudson (Winter Park FL). (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - F:HY Jean Cobb (Lynchburg VA). (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - F:HZ Bea Lester (English IN). (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - F:IB April 1994 New Bern NC and Montross VA Trip. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - F:IC Barbara Zinn (Long Beach CA). (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - F:ID Olivia James (Clarendon AR). (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - F:IE Lana J. Henley (Austin TX). (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - F:IE Lana J. Henley (Austin TX) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:IF Dorothy Mullan (Waco TX). (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - F:IG Helen Leone Paty Stamps (Oxford GA). (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - F:IH Mary Leggett (Alexandria VA). (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - F:IJ Wiley Wayne Todd (Livingston TX). (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - F:IK Don Brownlee (Northridge CA). (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - F:IL Leesburg, The Plains, Romney, Morgantown, and Pittsburgh Trip. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - F:IM Neath Painter (Coulter PA). (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - F:IN Scott Smith (Salt Lake City UT). (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - F:IO Princeton Library. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - F:IP John Carl Muse (Pittsburgh PA). (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - F:IQ Lee Muse (Snellville GA). (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - F:IR Margarie Butcher (Idabel OK). (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - F:IS LaVerne Markart (Sandy UT). (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - F:IT George H. Muse (Verona PA). (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - F:IW Earlene Muse (Odessa TX). (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - F:IV Clarence Johnson (Charleston SC). (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - F:IW William Anderson Hagey (Roanoke VA). (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - F:IX Christie Smith (Oklahoma City OK). (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - F:IY February 1995 King and Queen, Middlesex, and Essex Counties VA Trip. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - F:IZ Dale Stewart (Naperville IL). (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - F:JA Claire Furth (Chicago IL). (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - F:JB Dewey Whitfield Muse Jr. (Schaumburg IL). (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - F:JC Ruth Jenkins (Napa CA). (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - F:JD Judith Seager (Norman OK). (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - F:JE Robert Witherington (Winston-Salem NC). (Box 33, Folder 17-19)
  - F:JF Steven Rich (Rolla MO). (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - F:JG Donald Graves (Gulfport MS). (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - F:JH Vance McCollum (Jacksonville FL). (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - F:JI Lorene Rambo (Tempe AZ). (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - F:JK Cleve Kinnear (Claremore OK). (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - F:JL Jane Snyder (Montgomery AL). (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - F:JL June 1995 Virginia Courthouses. (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
  - F:JM Mildred Muse (Kernersville NC). (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - F:JM July 1995 Salt Lake City Trip. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - F:JN Claire Utt (Winfield KS). (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - F:JO Shelby Alexander (Lewisburg OH). (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - F:JP Sharon Van Tyne (Pilot Point TX). (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - F:JQ Sue Page (Lillian AL). (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - F:JR Patricia Brumit (Sun City West AZ). (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - F:JS Larry Muse (Baltimore MD). (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - F:JT F.C. "Ted" Mitchell (Gold River CA). (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - F:JV David Elrod (Prarie City IA). (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - F:JW James Edmundson (Clifton VA). (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - F:JW Rev. R. Wesley McLeod Jr. (Pinnacle NC). (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - F:JW Washington County (PA) Historical Society. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - F:JX Ken Baldwin (Greensboro NC). (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - F:JY Ernestine Forward (Inverness FL). (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - F:JZ Katherine Wood (Roanoke VA). (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - F:KA Pittsylvania County VA, UVA, Frederick MD Trip. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - F:KB Dee Seitel (Bozeman MT). (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - F:KC Peggy Mashburn (Rogersville AL). (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - F:KD Rick Gardner (Oconomowoc WI). (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - F:KE Mary Alice Ridout (Bracey VA). (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - F:KF James Hamblin (Montross VA). (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - F:KG Jo Ann (Williams) Huckaby (Overton TX). (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - F:KH Jo Ann Barnidge (Lafayette LA). (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - F:KI Scott Muse (Clovis NM). (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - F:KJ C.B. Fisher (Tulsa OK). (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - F:KK 1996 Muse Reunion. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - F:KL Wendy Kor (Olathe KS). (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - F:KM Hilda McKenzie (Flemingsburg KY). (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - F:KN Orla Reese (Wilmington DE). (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - F:KO Henry Harris (Chapel Hill NC). (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - F:KP Betty Davis (Kansas City MO). (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - F:KQ Robert Luther Muse (Winter Park FL). (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - F:KR Judith Wimberly (Conway AR). (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK). (Box 35, Folder 19-23)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:KS-2 Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK). (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK) - Family Group Sheets. (Box 36, Folder 3-5)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK) - Obituaries and Death Certificates. (Box 36, Folder 6-11)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK) - Obituaries and Death Certificates. (Box 37, Folder 1-6)
  - F:KS Donna Kiker Liddell (Midwest City OK) - Obituaries - Can't Locate Lineage. (Box 37, Folder 7-11)
  - F:KT Mrs. Marvin Garrett(Pace FL). (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - F:KW February 1997 Library of Virginia Trip. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - F:KV Ronald and Barbara Muse (Vienna VA). (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - F:KW Jeanne Whitney Muse (Asheville NC). (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - F:KX Margaret Liles (Montgomery AL). (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - F:KY Betty D. Six (Denver CO). (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - F:KZ Michelle Velten (Charlotte NC). (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - F:LA Jack Norford (Placida FL). (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - F:LA Jack Norford (Placida FL) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:LB Thomas L. Graves (Gulfport MS). (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - F:LC Bob Muse (Calif City CA). (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - F:LC Nancy Muse (Memphis TN). (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - F:LD Martha Burns (Winnsboro SC). (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - F:LD Michael Muse (Johnson City TN). (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - F:LD Katherine Marstaller (Austin TX). (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - F:LE Nora Smally (Livingston TX). (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - F:LE Shirley Clements (Daleville IN). (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - F:LF Mrs. Tommie Muse Amos (Dalton GA). (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - F:LG Chris Welch (Gainesville FL). (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - F:LH Donald C. Muse (Urbana IL). (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
  - F:LH George Muse (Erie PA). (Box 38, Folder 21-22)
  - F:LI Rowena Horr (Topeka KS). (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - F:LJ Linda Grider (Russell Springs KY). (Box 39, Folder 2-4)
  - F:LK Beth Thurmond (Athens GA). (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - F:LM Keri Southard (Bremerton WA). (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - F:LN R. Muse Brigman (Visalia CA). (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - F:LO Vickie Cole (Manassas VA). (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - F:LP June 1998 Mecklenburg, Union, Cabarrus, and Granville Counties NC Trip - Info on Kenneth Muse (Walt Disney). (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - F:LP Sherry Hurst Stoffers (Oakdale CA). (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - F:LQ, MG William Thompson (Colonial Beach VA). (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - F:LR Jean Day (Danville IN). (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - F:LS Patricia Holub (Riverside CA). (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - F:LT Paul Doherty (Berlin Germany). (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - F:LU Polly Dal Vera (Frisco CO). (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - F:LV Darlene Houseman (Baytown TX). (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - F:LW Juanita Griffin (Davidson OK). (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - F:LX Robin Horner Crew (Jackson AL). (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - F:LY Linda Ghormley (Prescott AR). (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - F:LZ Lynne Gantt (Great Falls VA). (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - F:MA Carol Lindsay (Dublin OH). (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - F:MB Kurt Muse (Fairfax VA). (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - F:MC Nathaniel Lee Muse (Gilmer TX). (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - F:MD Michele Roth (Sugarloaf CA). (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - F:ME Terry Moore (Raleigh NC). (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - F:MF Sandra Shellhammer (Illipolis IL) and Bill Bayles (Red Bluff CA). (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - F:MG, LQ Willam G. Thompson (Colonial Beach VA). (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - F:MH Mitch Muse (Jackson GA). (Box 40, Folder 5-9)
  - F:MI Lisa Chandley (Midland GA). (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - F:MJ Larry Muse (Urbanna VA). (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - F:MK David Muse (Perry GA). (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - F:ML Lianne Adams (Olympia WA). (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - F:MN Bobbie Joyce Chambliss (Quinlan TX). (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - F:MO Carman (Muse) Parker (Weatherford TX). (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - F:MP May-June 2000 Florida and Georgia Trip. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - F:MQ Dedra Routh (Franklinville NC). (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - F:MR Computer Sources (Ancestry.com/Vital Records Index). (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - F:MS (Sheila Slater (Newport NC). (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - F:MT Jay Muse/Howard Austin (Pittsburgh PA). (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - F:MU Descendants of Thomas Pope Muse. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - F:MV Ken Sutton (Fairfax VA). (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - F:MW Pat Bell Black (Clarksdale MS) and Terry D. Muse (Tulsa OK). (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - F:MX Kristie Muse (La Luz NM). (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - F:MY Nancy Evans (Arnold PA). (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - F:MZ Gene A. Burger. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - F:NA J.B. Childers (Fenwick Island DE). (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - F:NB Buddy Whiteaker. (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - F:NC Mike Nichol (Alberta Canada). (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - F:ND 1920 DC Census. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - F:NE Mary V. Long (Annapolis MD). (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - F:NF Iris Haden Wood (Mount Carmel IL). (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - F:NG Jaenn Bailey Smith (Greensboro NC). (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - F:NH Nancy Muse Reed. (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - F:NI M. Ruth Ingram Stultz (Silver Spring MD). (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - F:NJ Dal Mallory. (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - F:NK Jim Rheudasil (Tyler TX). (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - F:NL Billie Sutton Smith (Hollywood SC). (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - F:NM Inez Carney (Lakewood CO). (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - F:NM Inez Carney (Lakewood CO) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:NO T. Craig Mills (Denver CO). (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - F:NP Diane Bower (Dallas TX). (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - F:NQ Margaret Muse Cline. (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - F:NR Addie Grace Muse Alldaffer (Key West FL). (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - F:NS Louise Muse (Baltimore MD). (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - F:NT Ewell H. Muse III (Austin TX). (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - F:NW Vinette Muse Leinaar (Ocean Shores WA). (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - F:NV Lucy Todd (Bastrop TX). (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - F:NW Richard Muse m. Elizabeth Strother. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - F:NX Kay Muse. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - F:NY Gayland Muse. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - F:NZ Barbara Holbrook. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - F:NZ Barbara Holbrook (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:NZ Catherine Smith (Athens AL). (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - F:OA Bev and Andy Muse. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - F:OA Ruth O'Dell. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - F:OB Deanne Neff (Sonora CA). (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - F:OC Richard Muse. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - F:OD Larry D. Muse (Oklahoma City OK. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - F:OE Grant Harland Muse Jr. (Hot Springs SD). (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - F:OF Marigail Wynn (Earlysville VA). (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - F:OG British Ancestors. (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
  - F:OG Barbara Bursian (Haslett MI). (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - F:OH Lionel Bryson (West End NC). (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - F:OI Robert David Muse (Spring TX). (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - F:OJ James Edward Muse Jr. (Kentwood LA). (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - F:OK Oren Eugene Muse (Denner NC). (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - F:OL Wilma Dooley Muse (Fayetteville TN). (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - F:OM Donny Muse (Killen AL). (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - F:ON Charles Muse (Wilbraham MA). (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - F:OP Jack Muse (South Lyon MI). (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - F:OQ Sonny Seals. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - F:OR Larry Thomas Muse (Port Sanilac MI). (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - F:OS Daniel Skoubye (Apex NC). (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - F:OT Frederic Marshall Muse (Asheville NC). (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - F:OV Karl Muse (St. Augustine FL). (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - F:OW Jim Muse (Arlington VA). (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - F:OW Stacy Cole (Hornbeck LA). (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - F:OX Lee Muse. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - F:OY Dalton W. "Dal" Mallory. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - F:OY Scott Muse (Science Hill KY). (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - F:OZ Descendants of Morris Eli Muse. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - F:PA Robert Edward Muse Sr. (Ocean City MD). (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - F:PB Rear Admiral George Read Muse Lineage to Richard Muse (b. 1796) of Durham England. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - F:PC Samuel Muse (b. 1805) - Luzerne County PA. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - F:PD Janice M. Fry - NC Muses in the Civil War and Genealogical Reports by Dal Malloy. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - F:PE Donna Kiker Liddell (Oliver Otto Muse/James Oliver Muse Sr.). (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Craven and Beaufort Counties NC Muse Sheets. (Box 43, Folder 19-20)
  - England to Allegheny County PA. (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - England to Allegheny County PA (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - "James Muse III: Ancestors and Some Descendants" by Dr. Roger David Chambers. (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - "A Southern Legacy: Descendants of John Muse of Virginia" by Dr. Roger David Chambers. (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - "A Southern Legacy: Descendants of John Muse of Virginia - Volume II" by Dr. Roger David Chambers. (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Series III. Indexes., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 44-45)
  There are separate full-name indexes to the family group sheets for Muse and non-Muse surnames that contain the "identity code" used to locate a specific individual's sheet. In addition, there is a personal name index to the research/source files that includes the code used to locate a specific folder.
  - Index to Family Group Sheets (Muse and Non-Muse Surnames). (Box 44, Folder n/a)
  - Index to Research/Source Files. (Box 45, Folder n/a)